This type of neck opening/collar is a turtleneck.
What I have done is typically when we have a turtleneck, we will see it folded down and smooth.
What I did here was I'm representing it if you fold it all the way up.
If you don't flip it over.
You just have it standing up straight then it would have drape because obviously, this distance from your shoulder to your chin is not going to be as long as the neck on the shirt, the actual shirt, so it's going to end up bunching because you're going to have it pulled up and your neck is going to push it down.
So that's what I drew here.
But if you have a regular turtleneck, here I'll show you how to draw it if it's folded over.
Obviously these are drape lines.
So first do your little around the neck thing, and then this is the fold line, that's where it folds down over.
And there's our neckline seam.
And there's a turtleneck with it folded over.